{
    "id": "8615afbd967c4d7ebde53fa90ade1899",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You went there yesterday, ………………………?",
            "description": "Use a negative tag after an affirmative statement. In the simple past tense, use did in question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "did you",
                "didn't you",
                "hadn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71a3bc7bcda54258854c74a4016d9794"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had a word with your boss, …………………..?",
            "description": "Use did because this sentence is in the simple past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't you",
                "didn't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d855cf1cb934d898a06b06aa5af06bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told you something, ……………………………?",
            "description": "Use a negative tag after an affirmative statement. In the simple past tense, use did in question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "hadn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3b5c556f2af4cf0a487654b7c49c021"
        },
        {
            "question": "They live here, ………………………………?",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, use do or does to make question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "don't they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "103e538bff4f407e980d1667bb08a285"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an architect, ……………………….?",
            "description": "The auxiliary verb in the given statement is repeated in the question tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "doesn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1b49a3d2890466f99225fa24bbc65b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns a six figure salary, ……………………….?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. In the simple present tense, use do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "319d0f2a6ef943059197b7d96c7f1dca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spends a lot of money on gadgets, …………………………?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. In the simple present tense, use do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3627f8a93c74c2b9ff89acdb06ff298"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody knocked on the door, ………………………….?",
            "description": "Use they to refer to somebody, anybody, nobody etc in question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "did somebody",
                "did they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b3b13e66fabf464ca57ceff08de5dcde"
        },
        {
            "question": "That boy remembers everything, ……………………………?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. In the simple present tense, use do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a4314ddfc1b4860b4cffad83f8490c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team lost the match, ……………………………?",
            "description": "Use a negative tag after an affirmative statement. In the simple past tense, use did in question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "did we",
                "didn't they",
                "didn't we"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e49f1ef269dd467baf31bf1f95f28591"
        },
        {
            "question": "She travels around the world, …………………………..?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. In the simple present tense, use do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df89362f5d404b11b7c8103b5fe9d0be"
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t know him, …………………………………..?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. In the simple present tense, use do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a11b1fb1ccce466dad800e0b70416346"
        }
    ]
}